[Music]
hallelujah praise the
Lord before I even make a
prayer the
matter I'm about to address
today it's
um there there there is
Deliverance by casting out a demon but
there is Deliverance by releasing light
I
was and I I'll mention it here but I
discovered that when there is a demon
resident in a believer's not a believer
in a man's life it's an attack of
Destiny because when you when you have a
demon living in you it automatically
means that Spirit controls your life
life but now there is another level
where the spirit does not live in you
but the spirit shows up once in a while
and attacks
you so there is indwelling but there is
also attack a demon can live in a man
anytime a demon is resident in a man it
has everything to do with abortion of
Destiny but anytime a man
is not possessed but is affected by
demonic presence it means that spirit is
there to defile you and interrupt your
worship and communion with God so there
are certain levels of Revelations that
come upon a people so that now they are
able to understand and in their course
of action they act from a place of
understanding is that okay and some of
these teachings are highly
fought because you see in the book of
Hebrews there is a scripture that talks
about you know laying down the weight is
it Hebrew 13:1 or yes that's scripture
it it speaks about laying down every
weight and the sin that easily
entangles yes 121 it talks about laying
down every weight and the sin that
easily entangles and one of the things
are discover therefore we also since we
are surrounded by so great a cloud of
witness let us lay aside every weight
and the sin which so easily ens snares
us and let us run with endurance the
race that he said before us you can
never run if there is weight on
you that is why one of the things that
is always initiated and engineered from
the Demonic quarter is to make sure
there are things men are carrying so
that they are slow slow down on the race
of their
Destiny it is one thing for a man to
know destination is another thing for a
man to know Direction but it is another
thing for a man to have
motion I can know that this is where I
am going that's where I'm supposed to be
I can know that if I take this path I
will arrive but there is something that
has weighed me down that has affected my
mobility and in my motion and that's why
frustration is not lack of clarity of
Destiny frustration is when I cannot
lift my leg towards the right direction
and there are many believers who are
frustrated they know that this is not
where I'm supposed to be so please I
want to encourage you as we are making
this teaching listen carefully because
this will sort you and it will heal many
things in your life father in the name
of Jesus I take charge of this
environment I know that dear Lord this
is not just another message but this is
a king the real of the spirit this is
answers to nagging questions I pray for
the tongue of a teacher and I pray for
the wisdom of sages I declare that this
will be practical and something that is
going to deliver your sons and daughters
and even today before the end of the
service them that are bound will be let
loose and certain doors will be closed
and there will be Freedom the Bible says
where the holy spirit is there is
Liberty there is Liberty in the house
today I declare let the hearing ear be
open and let the Seeing Eye also be open
to see the light and the Revelation that
you are about to speak to us thank you
Lord and thank you for entrusting us
even with this message in Jesus name and
somebody say Amen you can have your
seats amen even as we appreciate the
worshippers let's put our hands together
as we appreciate the
worshippers I want to appreciate the
online
community people watching from different
areas of the globe I've seen some people
watching from Turkey
Australia uh someone texted and said
Rwanda is represented in the house so we
bless the Lord for the ability to reach
the globe through online also want to
appreciate them that we labor with I see
Pastor Eugene may God bless you thank
you for the prayers and the Declaration
someone someone wrote and said he's
praying like Pastor T so I've seen how I
pray may God bless you I don't know am I
the one praying like you or the one
praying like me but either of us but
that's the seed of sunship I want to
appreciate Pastor Ken joou may God bless
you um thank you for coming I want to
appreciate uh K Jaguar's wife in the
house uh may God bless you I want to
appreciate Pastor William and Pastor
Purity may God bless you I want to
appreciate um pastor Kevin with your
wife wife God bless you and in a special
way I want to appreciate my wife who is
also in the house and for the sake of
visitors I'll ask my wife to stand amen
just in case you have ever heard of any
rumor or suggestion let me clear the air
this is my
wife
Hallelujah yeah that's my wife and I
love her very much and there is no other
she's the one and only
amen now I want to dive straight in the
word and I want us to look at soul ties
I we are still on the
series living to cleave leave to
cleave but I will have I call this title
singly
single singly single because you can be
numerically single in the reals of men
but you are married in the reals of the
spirit
that's why I'm calling it singly single
because there are men that are
contending with the Gate of marriage and
until they understand you must be singly
single then it means there are a few
things that may not answer very well I
remember before I got married I went to
my spiritual
mother and I told her I found a wife and
I want to marry her because the Bible
says a man shall live his father and
mother and find a wife the the Bible
does not have definitions of girlfriends
uh because there is a there is a level
where a woman and a there is a level
where a girl becomes a woman and there
is a level where that woman becomes a
wife and not every woman is your wife
that's why you need to understand you
are not compatible with everybody and so
I told her I found a wife and and she
told she asked me how old are you I told
the mom I'm 33 32 turning to 33 and she
asked me she told me I have heard of
your testimonies and they are not very
good the man that died that man was not
a good man and she told me go and
separate yourself from any woman you
ever had a relationship with and she
told me you can take two weeks or one
week and this what she told me
if you're going to pray or not to pray
it's your destiny and your life I love
my mother she's radical like that and I
knew that if I don't deal with soul ties
connections and relationships that were
there before it is possible for me to
walk down the aisle but I'm not
single and I get joined to a woman and
if she was not also careful to deal with
things in her pth p is possible for two
single men numerically to be married but
there is a lot of Chaos in the reals of
the spirit so when we talk about Soul
Time the definition
is a salai is Souls becoming knitted
together and becoming one
flesh I'll give you different
definitions because there are different
types of su TI and and so every
definition suits a certain type soul
ties is Souls becoming
knitted
knitted knitted together and becoming
one
flesh Souls becoming knitted together
and becoming one flesh the second
definition is a deep
spiritual a deep
spiritual and emotional connection to
another
individual a deep spiritual and
emotional connection to another
emotional connection con connection to
another
individual the other definition
is is rooted in
bond rooted in bond between two people
are rooted in in bond between two people
formed through
emotional spiritual or physical
connection rooted in
bond that rooted in bond it's
deep between two people formed through
emotional spiritual or physical
connection you look at the the three of
them there are words here that are very
key the first definition has the word
knitted something that is knitted
together needs a certain technicality to
unit it something that is
deep it means it take some levels of
understanding for a man to get out of it
something that is rooted it means it has
been there for a
while now when we look at soul ties suti
can be good and they can also be
bad Su TI can be good and they can be
bad because in the context of marriage
Sal TI is
good but in the context of a broken
marriage soul ties are not good or even
a broken
relationship so Sal TI can be good
especially when it is between a husband
band and a wife I'll want my soul to be
knitted together with that of my wife
when people stay together for long they
begin to resemble each
other and not only do they resemble each
other sometimes there are times I talk
and my wife will finish the statement
for me we are so knitted that she knows
what I'm supposed to say next sometimes
I will even call and she's like I was
just calling you
because there is such a
connection uh in the in the soul that
that that that that we are
one there are even people there there
even a connection between parents and
children that a mother can call you and
she's almost 100 kilomet away but she's
able to pick a signal that you're not
okay because your relationship with your
mother connected you and developed a
certain Bond
so soul ties can be good because they
help the knitting and they help all
these things but they can also be bad
especially when now there is people
breaking up and things and relationships
are not working so we are not here to
demonize the whole thing because that
connection in marriage is very powerful
and very
key and there are four types of soul
ties there are four of them four types
of soul ties
there are four types of soul ties number
one we have emotional soul ties number
one we have emotional soul ties what is
emotional Soul tie emotional soul ties
involve intense feeling of
attachment an emotional salty involves
intense feeling of
attachment why is this attachment
there it is there because this emotional
Soul TI is created when you share
sentimental or very personal and
secretive
things this intense attachment is
created when you share sentimental
things or very personal and secretive
things it is created when you share
sentimental things or very personal and
secretive
things I know we have heard of cases or
a pastor slept with a
member and sometimes we wonder how can
that happen the man of God knows the
truth but also the member knows he's a
man of
God how dare are
you but you when you you begin to
understand
counseling there are members who become
vulnerable with the man of God because
sometimes a person will come and fail to
understand that we are men of God we are
not gods of
men so you begin to talk to a man but
he's of God and you begin to share very
personal
issues uh you can work on my monitors
you begin to share very personal
issues and what you don't know is that
you are opening up your heart and
opening up your life and suddenly you
even feel like there is a connection and
attachment to that
person that's why sometimes pastor's
wives are
hated because the women you have celed
and they Shar their very personal issues
they begin to look at you with with
certain eyes so when they hear Pastor
saying and that's my wife they're not
clapping and they don't even know they
are being irritated
subconsciously because naturally when a
person becomes vulnerable to another
person they begin to open doors and they
feel like they are naked before
you that's why there are people
especially women there are people you
disagree with oh my God
H when women
disagree the intensity of
hatred is so much not because you might
even realize it is not that that person
did anything big no it's because the
person I have disagreed with is like
that person has carried a part of me
because she knows too much about
me and we see this one in the book of 1
Samuel 18 and
verse1 1st Samuel 18 and
verse1 this emotional salty is common
between friends and especially the
people we call best of
friends 1 Samuel 18 and verse1 these was
David and David had such a deep
connection with
Jonathan even some men in their
perversive thinking always say that this
scripture here reveals that David was
gay
Madness the Bible says now when he had
finished speaking to Saul the soul of
Jonathan was down what was need to the
soul of David and Jonathan loved him as
his own
soul and we see this friendship that
Jonathan
surrendered the opportunity to become a
king because when Saul became a king in
the pattern Israel requested for a king
in the pattern of other nations so in
the other nations the law of monarchy
was when the King dies the son takes
over so according to Saul Jonathan was
meant to be next in command but
according to prophecy and Revelation
David was meant to be next in command
now we see that there was such a
connection between Jonathan and David to
appoint Jonathan surrendered his right
according to monarchy towards the throne
and offered it to David and even
preserved and protected David from the
wrath of his father so now this bond
that KN there that's a soul TI it's an
emotional Soul
TI it's an emotional Soul
TI and that's why when couples stay for
long they develop emotional
bond and this is the reason why some
breakups are
messy because you can break up with a
man and go and live in America but you
are still hurting in America you are not
in Kenya you can't even see the man or
the woman but there is a lot of
emotional investment that because of
that investment no matter the distance
there is still
connection you can see the picture of
your ex
picture he's in Qatar as you see it on
Facebook you begin to
cry and you feel the anger as if it's
fresh am I speaking to anyone because
there is a connection emotionally people
that you spend time together for long
people that you have opened your heart
and shared very personal secrets and
personal issues no matter how far they
go you'll always feel their
presence you can be miles away but
distance does not sort this out and I'll
share wisdom and this wisdom for Mees to
work for you remember pastors are not
God please save
us a woman came in my office one day my
wife is heavily pregnant and she comes
in my office
lamenting and crying and saying pastor
my husband has been in Qatar for 2 years
2 years and then she comes and tells me
for two years Pastor I've not been
intimate with my husband so I feel like
asking her as a pastor how should I help
you am I making sense tell your neighbor
neighbor
so I realized I needed to communicate
wisdom to her and I said number one you
either join the man in
Qatar because when he was going you knew
he was
going number two is you sit down as a
family and ask between marriage and job
which is important but at the end of the
day a decision must be made and it will
not be made by Pastor it will be made by
you as a
couple so please and I'm not saying that
again it is
okay but always know there is a level
only God can help you this has made so
many people to be vulnerable you just go
and share be sensitive with who you open
your heart
to because it can also open a door of
manipulation look at the Book of Judges
chapter number 16 and verse
16 it can open a door of manipulation
people that know so much about you they
can become tools of
manipulation now Judges
16:16 Judges
16:16 and it came to pass when she
pested him daily with her words and
pressed him so that his soul was vexed
to death go to the next one see what
Samson did that he told her
all his heart and said to
her this is now
Samson opening up his life to
Delilah there was a level of trust
Delilah is a prostitute Delilah is in
business Samson is in love
Delilah has been paid to know the source
of Samson power Samson has been anointed
to deal with the generation and the seed
that Delila
represents I don't know why sometimes we
become victims of opening up to the
wrong
people this is a prostitute with a man
who is a Nazarite the the the man was
announced by an Angel that was the birth
of
Samson it was an Angelic
announcement he was in the same level as
Jesus and John those were the only men
he's the only man in the Old Testament
who an angel came to announce his
birth and now he's here with a woman
who's paid to know the source of his
power and the man opens up his heart for
I have I have been a Nazarite to God
from my mother's womb and then he says
if I'm shaven then my strength will
leave me and I shall become weak and be
like any other man meaning that the man
was not like other men there is a
preservation when men stay in ordination
never think you are you are ordinary oh
my God that that peculiar even the world
knows some people think why am I not
attracting men in my life
listen men know what to
Value I remember there was a girl in
campus who decided to backslide and on
that day of her backsliding she went to
the campus cafeteria where they were
selling alcohol and there was a man who
was a terrorist he was known he would
come with girls and buy them alcohol and
the girl was a c leader she was known
long dresses she came out with a tight
and a T-shirt and she walked in and when
went and sat there and she said today I
want to take alcohol the chairman in
charge of alcohol looked at her and said
this Committee of men we know in this
campus who wife materials are and you're
are one of them and the man bought the
girl Pana and she was escorted to her
room and other girls were left on that
table drinking alcohol and I think it
was a communication is that I man Chapa
the the people that that value
themselves we value
them yeah am I speaking to
anyone so please tell that neighbor
neighbor value and value attracts what
value so don't lower your value don't
try to play gorah here when you're in
Manchester what Ma you
know okay let let me stick to scripture
but I have to speak to a generation
please don't lower your value trying to
fit in the one that the Lord has
prepared for you must match up in your
level don't come down to pick him let
that person come up to find you because
you begin to see now immediately the man
confessed his secret something began to
happen he said I've been peculiar I've
been unique I know there is something
about my hair look at the next
scripture when deila saw that he had
told her all his heart so a woman can
know when a man has spoken his
heart if if I was to translate this
in she sent and called for the Lords of
the Philistines saying come up once more
for he has told me all his heart so the
lord of the philistine came up to her
and brought the money in their
hand this was
business and when this man look look at
now at the vulnerability of Samson he's
thinking now they're
playing look at this said please
continue go to the next one then she led
him to sleep on her knees it is not here
it is here it's called
ties a man can find Comfort on the boss
s of his wife or the breast of his
mother and if that does not happen he
might also find comfort in the thighs of
the
ler a man analyzed this scripture and
said there are many men sleeping on
dea's
ties because the bossom of their wives
is not
available you can see this woman
provided a very demonic
atmosphere for the man to feel
comfortable when we were rappers we used
to say you cannot lay your head on the
thighs of theila and wake up in
Abraham's bosom
and led him to
sleep and called for a man and had him
shave off the Seven Locks of his end
then she began to torment him and his
strength left
him I discover that people we open our
hearts to if they are not mature to
handle us with our secrets and things we
consider sentimental they can manipulate
us that's why there is that
ex he knows the buttons to
press I'm opening the seven seal and
expected
silence you have been telling the Lord
this year is the year of
advancement but you you you you even
deleted his number but you or her number
but you have their number
offered so the problem is not whether
it's in the phone the problem is that
you still have the number and now that
person either a girl or a man they know
the button to press you look at a phone
ringing you ignore a phone ringing you
ignore then the man will send a text or
the woman will send a text and saying
please when you go to church pray for my
mother she's not okay and then she knows
there is a button of Mercy in you and
then you say if the mother is sick let
me just know the mother and you're
like mother ask
so the agenda is not M it's a Buton I
know that
ah I know you care I know you are
merciful and I know I just need to
raise I need to guilt trip
you yes
yes and when you refuse to answer to
that SMS and the man will begin out to
manipulate your emotions you know if I'm
even depressed I'm even suicidal this is
the only mom I have I I wish I wish you
are just here to hold hands with me and
you begin to feel guilty but the way the
man terrorized your
heart the way that woman tortured you
but they know the butons why because one
day you are taken in a corner and they
just brought a dead
chicken dead
chicken it doesn't matter what they
called it grilled baked it was a dead
chicken and some pressed either crushed
or fried potatoes and that became the
key of your conversation and you began
to open your
heart oh my God eat and go
home tell your neighbor emotional Soul
TI it's a serious matter because I say
there is a place for it when it happens
in the confinement of marriage it's a
blessing when it happens outside or and
this is why people never overcome their
excess can I even be can I go further
this is why a man or a woman can enter
marriage but they are still emotionally
connected to people they were
dating you have your wife there or you
have your husband there and anytime you
disagree with your wife or your husband
there is always a demonic thing that
comes and ask
you and then you begin to say if so and
so was the one here this matter he or
she would have handled it
differently they say the success of the
Germans in
war is that any time they went to a
territory the first thing is that they
offloaded their ship after offloading
their ship they used to set their ships
on
fire so that the Sheep cannot take them
back from where they were coming from
and that's where they were talking about
no retreat nor surrender so by the time
they are now getting in the territory
they know there is no way back some
people left the Sheep like
Peter you remember the Bible says and
when when Elisha was stopped by Elijah
what did he do he went and told Elisha
if I have to pursue you and pursue this
relationship I must set on fire the
things that I used to do he went and
slaughtered his oxen set them on fire
and pursued the man there are men that
have refuse to set their sheep on fire
and that's why anytime things are not
working they run back to the
ship and if there is a plan B I know
right now there's something going around
on Tik Tok there DEA
DEA people are looking at the bank and
they're saying Plan B listen if there is
a plan B plan a will not
work for marriages to work you must
enter knowing there's no
exit by the way it is not a good thing
when people begin to
say that means there is a potential exit
door there there are words that men must
avoid avoid the words it's better to
insist on solving than
dissolving there are people who
perpetually confess about divorce words
are powerful and one day shall be a
reality it's better you focus on how can
we solve because dissolving is the
easiest thing somebody say emotional
salty somebody say emotional Sal TI and
can I tell you something you know the
problem with emotions it it takes time
to heal I'll not lie to
you it doesn't take a service for a man
that is broken or messed up to heal it
takes
time I wish there was something like a
soap called anti- emotions that you just
go and shower and you come out like a
ninja
but it takes
time and and you know when we begin to
talk about these things they are so
Paramount because when a man is
emotionally damaged even his connection
to God is
affected look at the book of First Kings
Second Kings uh chapter 3 beginning from
verse one second Kings chapter 3 it
hinders
relationship I remember there are days
there's a time I was going through a
heartbreak I will go to church and I
will not pray but I'm in church I'm
singing and I'm crying but no
prayer 2 Kings 3 now jeram the son of
Ahab became king over Israel at Samaria
in the 18th year of Jehosaphat king of
Judah and reigned 12
years continue and he did evil in the
sight of the Lord but not like his
father and mother for put away the sacri
pill of Bal that his father had
made nevertheless he persisted in the
sins of joban the son of nabat who had
made Israel sin he did not depart from
them now mesha King of Moab was a sheep
breeder and he regularly paid the king
of Israel 100,000 lambs and two and the
wool of 100,000
Rams this was like a TI but it happened
when Ahab died that the king of Moab
rebelled against the king of
Israel so King jehoram went out of
Samaria at that time and mastered all
Israel then he went and sent to
Jehoshaphat king of Judah saying the
king of Moab has rebelled against me
will you go with me to fight against
Moab and he said I will go up I am as
you are my people as your people my
horses as your horses then he said which
way shall we go up and he answered by
the way of the Wilderness of
Edom so the king of Israel went with the
king of Judah and the king of Edom and
they march on that thr about route 7even
days and there was no water for the Army
nor for the animals that followed them
and the king of Israel said alas for the
Lord has called these three kings
together to deliver them into the hand
of Moab but Jehoshaphat said is is there
no prophet of the Lord here that we may
inquire of the Lord by him so one of the
Servants of the king of Israel answered
and said elishah the son of shaat is
here who poured water on the hands of
Elijah that's how they described him he
was a man of service and Jehoshaphat
said the word of the Lord is with him so
the king of Israel and Jehoshaphat and
the king of Edom went down to him now
look everybody read then Elisha said to
the king of Israel what have I to do
with you go to the prophets of your
father and the prophets of your mother
but the king of Israel said to him no
for the Lord has called these three
kings together to deliver them into
their hands there was a problem with
elishah when it CES to his emotions he
was a short-tempered
man and because he realized that problem
look at what he
did look at the next one and elishah
said as the Lord of H live before must
stand surely were it not that I regard
the presence of Jehosaphat king of Judah
I will not look at you nor see you
and then he said but now do what bring a
musician so that my soul can settle and
when my soul is settled I can hear God
so when a man is emotionally
starred even his fellowship with God is
altered because it was possible for the
man to prophesy from a solish level out
of his anger and hatred and and you know
how he perceived the Kings he would have
spoken to them in that level and now he
had to tell them you must bring a
musician a man that can generate an
atmosphere for
Fellowship look at the Book of Luke
chapter number four beginning from Verse
18 Luke chapter number four beginning
from Verse
18 when I saw this it kind of opened
dimensions and I realized that this is a
serious matter Luke 4:18 the spirit of
the Lord is upon me because he has
anointed me to preach the gospel to the
poor look at this one what has he done
he has sent me to do what to
heal the
brokenhearted meaning that the Lord is
concerned about your emotional
status you know this is Jesus declaring
why he
came this is him now opening the scroll
and trying to summarize what we call the
Mandate of his appearance the spirit is
upon me one to preach the gospel and he
has sent me to heal the brokenhearted
because where men live with men they
will break each other but there is an
anointing that can heal the
brokenhearted there is a place where
counseling cannot penetrate but the balm
of Gilead can release his oil and heal
your heart that a man you are looking
with eyes of Vengeance you can now look
at him and say God bless you do I
condemn
you one of my relatives came and she
told me I want us to pray for my
marriage because um the husband had
walked out and this was the worst case
the man walked out and went and married
next door so when he's driving you know
he's the one and then now he has left a
very good home and he has rented a beder
in the next compound and he has left a
good house and and you know naturally
the prayer will be father we scatter
this marriage we call the man back to
his home and those are prayers of anger
and bitterness so as I went to prayer
the Lord told me pray tell tell your
relative to pray for her heart and her
peace because the Lord is not a
dictator the Lord will not go and pinch
that man and tell him come here this is
your wife and these are your children
and there are many people and I'm not
saying God cannot restore a broken
marriage or relationship is someone
getting me but when you begin to
understand the science of free will is
that the Lord will generate an
environment for that person to hear the
truth but the Lord will obey the
decision of the
man okay so the Lord will not force the
man but the Lord will obey and respect
his decision and if there are any
consequence es and repercussions the
Lord will also watch as they happen
because it's called Free
Will so in this scenario I said you have
to pray for your heart because what you
need in this matter is not the man you
need
peace because the man can come and you
see him in the house but he still has
his other relationships what you need is
your personal peace and we began to pray
for peace and I tell you the truth there
was such an anointing that peace Came
Upon her and one day the man drove in
the house and she opened the door told
the man you can sit down served the man
food and called the children and said
come and say hi to your father and the
man looked at the food and he didn't eat
said no this this is poison you can't I
know how I have messed you up you can't
just treat me like this because the man
was was coming from a place of guilt but
the woman was coming from a place of
Peace because the bound of Gilead has
the power to appro that bitterness and
take that heart and release his peace
and his Joy
ah I feel like having
touch I feel like having
touch hey I know there are people who've
separated but they have never even
agreed on coparenting if any time they
pick a call is war because these are two
bitter people and it's just a simple
matter the child needs diapers but the
way that man will
behave he has money but his ego he's
saying I cannot go down
fast and the child is
suffering and the woman is bitter and
she will begin to type smss that don't
end
there is no peace for the wicked they
sleep and they never sleep one day God
will lift
me I know you hate me and and the man is
looking at the message and you realize
unless the Lord heals the woman and the
man this child will become the
playground of the emotional
temperaments and I'm not here to
encourage separations is someone getting
me but there is a place first when you
realize things are not working out pray
for your heart before you pray for the
other
person am I speaking because there are
men dragging a man on the altar when
they are bleeding drag Yourself fast on
the Altar and tell the Lord Heal Me fast
before I begin to pray for that woman or
that man this thing is serious because
when a person is messed up emotionally
many things go wrong this is where
depressions comeing you can have
everything in life but when you are
emotionally unstable you don't enjoy
them you can be in a luxar car a luxara
home but when you are messed up
emotionally it doesn't help you and
that's why you need to pray the Bible
calls it the peace that surpasses human
understanding how can you be smiling and
we know your husband has four
wives how comes you are adding weight
and we know your wife left
you because there is a peace called the
peace that passes human understanding
even me I cannot understand it but I
know there is a God who came for the
Brokenhearted someone getting
me and this is a very powerful prayer
because it can slow you down in life it
can hinder progression and and let me
also put this and I speak now as a
father I speak as a father never stop
your
vision never stop your vision
thinking that it is love for you to
suspend your vision to support another
person's
Vision it is not love it is
foolishness I have seen men who decided
to cross the ocean for her and they
drowned because they were not good in
swimming I have seen and many of the
people that get affected are women
because naturally a woman is designed
with a womb and one of the thing is that
a woman is cultured to
reciprocate so the moment you love a
woman the best thing she can do is
suspend her life and look like now
whatever you are doing is what we are
going to do and I have seen women who
gave their all to a man when the man
rose up slay Queens began to see him
that man is made is a a product of a
woman that labor to see the man rise now
he's trying to disguise and look down on
the woman who is the woman that prayed
with him who is the woman that believed
in his dream when he was a nobody who is
the woman that sacrificed all to see the
man rise and then the man forgets and
the woman looks at her life three
children she's now 42 years and she's
asking even if I was to get married
who'll marry
me and then you ask her she tells you oh
no you know I retired and then when my
imp came I gave him when I look at my
life I'm now depressed women listen to
me never abandon your
dream because of a man that man can also
die what will you
do people have been left
widowed I'm speaking to you now and also
in your future never that Vision you had
as a young girl don't kill it that
Vision you had as a young man don't kill
it so one day I'm going through breakup
and I lost
weight I was thin I was not eating and I
decided to look at that girl she was in
Mombasa she had added weight her face
was glowing that was my wakeup call and
in those in two years I used to sing I
did not record any song I almost got
fired from my job as as someone was
going on with their life as if I didn't
exist I wish you can know you you are
losing sleep when someone is
snoring you are turning every side like
a goalkeeper when someone is dead asleep
my goodness may peace locate you I say
may peace locate you may every broken
heart be healed there is a level only
God can
enter hey Manu is that you
okay oh you are saying hallelujah on
behalf of boo okay s
s
okay the second one is what we call
physical Soul tie physical Soul
tie physical soul is a deep this is a
deep energetic connection a deep
energetic connection formed between two
people is a deep energetic connection
formed between two
people mainly through physical intimacy
like
sex a deep energetic connection formed
between two people mainly through
physical intimacy like
sex and naturally it leaves emotional
impact it leaves emotional
impact and sense of closeness in a
bodily level sense of closeness in a
bodily level even after the
relationship a deep energetic
connection a deep energetic connection
formed between two
people primarily through physical
intimacy primarily through physical
intimacy like sexual
contact Living a lasting emotional
impact
living a lasting emotional impact and
sense and sense of
closeness in a bodily
level even after the
relationship I repeat the last time a
deep energetic
connection formed between two people
primarily through physical intimacy like
sexual contact living a lasting
emotional impact and sense of closeness
in a bodily level even after
relationship
ends 1 Corinthians 6
15-17 First Corinthians 6:15
to17 this physical suti is majorly
connected to sexual intercourse do you
know that your body bodies are members
of Christ shall I then take the members
of Christ and make them members of aot
certainly
not or do you not know that he who is
joined to a harot is one body with her
for the two he says shall become one
flesh you see when people come to the
altar
we always declare that now we announce
so and so to be
husbands or husband and wife that
declaration is a confirmation of the
Covenant but the cealing of that
Covenant can only happen in the setup of
honeymoon I know of a lady who even
signed the contract
but it's a it's a strange
story they walked down the
aisle and when they walk down the
aisle they came and they were declared
husband and
wife and then the man looked at the lady
and say today is
today and something told the lady this
man is not marrying you for Destiny he's
marrying to prove a
point and the lady walked out of that
wedding she didn't even go for the
reception and she didn't even sign that
government
thing now because there was no
consumation whatever was announced on
the altar was not
sealed is someone getting me and when
she walked out there was a lot of upro
and later it was true I think they
discovered the guy
was funny or anything but I bless the
Lord the lady got married and now she's
serving the
lord so we need to understand that when
it comes to intimacy or
sex in the eyes of Heaven it is not a
tool of pleasure I know we don't talk
about these things in
church but we hear them every day in the
radio so I said I want to be a balanced
preacher I will not ignore what men are
going through on Earth simply because
you are going to heaven
and so you realize that one man wrote
and said I was listening to a preacher
and he said when they introduced
contraceptives they
reduced the seriousness of
sex when they introduced abortion they
dealt with the consequences of
sex when contraceptives were introduced
they killed the seriousness and abortion
killed the concept of the results or the
consequences of
sex it was so funny that during the
Kamala Harris campaign it was so radical
that the Democrats as the woman is
selling her policy there is a certain
state where they had abortion boots and
they even came and gave a feedback that
five people have
aborted and now you begin to see to look
at how sex has been handled in
communities that are considered
liberal you realize it has lost his
place in fact you'll be so surprised
that 50% of our high schoolers are
sexually active
50% the word active means possibly every
holiday they having sex I met with
someone and they were giving me the
statistics and they said the withdrawal
of this us Aid funding not only does it
predispose about the 2 million people
that have been on air
but they are now saying there is
a
alarming
Spike and Rise of HIV infection among
teenagers between 13 to 19 that is the
most
infected I'm waiting for December to see
the data on the world's a day but I
think the other December they they said
they are accounting to around 50% and
this is the number of every year the
last time I checked the data every year
more than 30,000 young people were
getting infected so if we don't have
this conversation from the altar we will
lose a generation
scene you know this this tent possibly
we around
1,500 even if we blow the number and say
2,000 so you can imagine is such T 15 of
them full that is before the end of the
year full of Destinies and now the
problem is there is a lot of inter
generational sex through what we are
calling
mangaba Mama so that tells me if this is
the most affected generation then and
there is intergenerational sex there is
a lot of transfer and what are the muas
doing if I'm married then it means I'm
also predisposing my family into chaos
the web is a technical
web it is God who created sex
I tell you today sex is so available and
it is not even about who is chasing who
even women are chasing men that's how
bad it is that's the society we are
living in
today and so we begin to see that when
you now look at the
spirituality and the bibilical
understanding of sex number one when a
woman came she came H as a virgin she
had a certain thing called the highman
and when she lost her virginity there
was blood
shed that blood was meant to be the
entity that seals the Covenant of
marriage according to
ordination meaning that the first time
consumation was meant to happen was
after declaration that you're are a
couple and you have entered into a
covenant and the Covenant is sealed by
the
blood that's the bibilical pattern
and that's why even the Jewish culture
they were like the Muslim a man will go
and have intercourse with the wife and
the men will confirm in the morning
whether the consumation was sealed by
Blood whether that Covenant was
there now of course nowadays
um being a virgin is not something we
talk about talk about secondary
virginity but I know there are still
people who are upholding which is a good
thing and that's why you look at Jesus
in Matthew 19 and verse
99 Jesus mentioned something that is
very radical Matthew 19 and ver9
something that is very radical these
were the disciples asking him about
marriage and he comes and says and I
said to you and they were asking is it
right to divorce because Moses had
opened that channel that when you get
tired you can give a woman
divorce talak she goes so they were
asking Jesus is it right to divorce and
Jesus had to correct the matter and said
it was not so in the beginning because
in the beginning God created Adam and
Eve a man and a woman if God intended
for man to be polygamous he would have
created a man and two
women why did he create a man and a
woman because that is the image of
Christ and the church so Christ does not
have two Brides so if I have to model
the image of Christ and the church then
one must must be Christ and the other
one must be the church and the man plays
the role of Christ the woman plays the
role of the church and then jesus takes
them to the foundation what we call the
law of the first mention he took them to
Genesis and then he says this is the
reason and I said to you whoever
divorces his wife
except for sexual
immorality sexual immorality why because
it is by the channels of sex that Two
Become One it means that person has been
enjoined to another
person and this was not just sexual
immorality as we are looking at it from
our side this sexual immorality in the
Greek and interpretation what Jesus
meant except by the laws of
ponia it is called the laws of ponia
they are found in Leviticus chapter
number
18 the laws of pon
they are found in Leviticus chapter
number 18 it talks about
adultery it talks about
fornication it talks about
bestiality it talks about incest and it
talks about
gazing it talks about
fornication
adultery
incest
incest this is relatives having
sex with other relatives it talks
about
bestiality and it also talks about
homosexuality now those are the laws of
ponia you know in our
day and I'm saying this and you need
need to get me with balance if I was to
bring a man who is born again and I tell
you um this is a church Elder and he has
a wife and Aang CLE and this is a
teenager and she's a lesbian the church
WIll condemn the
lesbian because we have been configured
to understand that lesbianism is a
bigger sin but cheating in your marriage
is not sin according to the law of ponia
Leviticus 18 they're in the same
category and they are called
Abominations you shall keep my ordinance
so that you do not commit any of these
AB abominable Customs which were
committed before you and that you do not
defile yourselves by them I am the Lord
your God see the matter go to Matthew 19
and verse
10 I want you to see the feedback of the
disciples I want you to see the feedback
of the disciples Matthew 19 and: 10 for
there are you everybody read for his
disciples said to him if such is the
case of the man with his wife it is
better if Jesus was to come and teach
today you will change your mind on
marriage I'm not here to tell you to
change but we have now to bring the
ordinance of this matter so this soul
ties sex is
beyond physical when you go back to that
scripture in 1 Corinthians 6:15 you go
from 16 and 17 you realize that it is
beyond physical sex is the only thing
that addresses the man in totality it
will address your mind address your body
and address your
spirit do you not know that your bodies
are members shall take the member of
Christ and make them members of H
certainly not look at the next one or do
you not know that he who is joined to a
harot is one body with her for the two
he says shall become one flesh now look
at the other one go to the next one but
he who is joined to the Lord is one
spirit with
him that's what he looks at it so this
is beyond go to the next
one everybody read flee sexual
immorality every sin that a man does is
outside the body but he who commits
sexual immorality sins against his
own when you begin to look at this
matter is serious and that's why there
is a lot of emotional
investment before
intercourse there's a lot either
party people used to come when we in
campus people are naughty and they were
saying oh we are friends with benefits
not relationship and in that
organization of friends with benefit one
person will fall in
love you can't just surrender yourself
as a tool of
pleasure there is a lot of connections a
lot of emotions a lot of
dying and sometimes again and I'm sorry
to say
this when a woman is loved
right she will look around her
ecosystem and realize there's nothing
else I can give other than
myself and sometimes
men because of their logical
inclination a man can have sex as a form
of
relief no connection nothing but there
is for for for a woman that's why the
more you begin that's why even sometimes
I'm sensitive even if it's a favor I'm
very sensitive because the moment you
begin to treat a woman in a certain way
genuinely even if your heart is genuine
you will begin to feel like what can I
do to this
man to show him that I'm
grateful because they are creatures of
reciprocation
Hallelujah that's why this thing of
becoming Father Abraham you want to help
every sister in church my brother please
if you have a wife let your wife become
the channel of supply
if money has to be sent to someone let
your wife be the one to say my husband
has told me to send you this
money you are trying to program that
woman not to think not to be
creative some will even tell you I know
you are
married if that door is
opened watch Mama let every every money
passed through
her I go
father those private
counselings it can't be that all you do
is canel women and you're a brother you
are in fault you are not
married but now you are the
prefect you are Mr
wisdom you know there are people who
come and they want to see me and I tell
them uh that matter I pass it to my wife
very few follow up with her and if you
dishonor my wife you have Dishonored me
because we are one you can't love me and
hate her because she's a part of
me so let ask her that lady she has
never called
and I'm not giving you a referral
because there are things I know as a man
I can't deal with them and I feel like d
to D that make sense I need to know I'm
a
man pastors are you hearing me yes I
know we love our members
but you see Li she's a woman of God my
is a woman of God mature the matter you
sharing unless I talk to you with my
wife Hallelujah
now I I I can say a lot about sex but
what I know is that sex is what binds in
marriage that is what
binds and when you begin to hear people
talking about body counts that's a very
technical
matter because a man not only comes as a
man there are things a man carries can I
do a demonstration you understand let me
just have come pastor Kevin come Pastor
Eugene
please
come you know what people don't know is
that let's assume pastor Kevin
here there are things in his life they
are very spiritual
witchcraft he has some generational
patterns he's
suicidal there he those are things in
his spirit and his soul and here we have
you know Eugene there are also things
that he carries in him possibly there
are cures in his
family Spirit of
poverty he doesn't keep a job he's
perpetually fired and here is
Li now this is Liz Liz was with Kevin
and then they broke up
but in this relationship there was
intercourse what she doesn't know there
was transfer of
things she comes from a family where
marriages never work so there are things
she transfers spiritually and there are
things he transfers spiritually so by
the time she's breaking up with Kevin
the fact that Kevin is not in her life
there are certain behaviors that she has
collected so by the time they are
meeting with you
again there are things she has collected
she was innocent now she's now coming
ready for marriage she's a cocktail of
all these things she collected and there
are also things she left in these
brothers by the time she's discovering
she's now suicidal she has never even
become suicidal but now there is a
depressive
Spirit the Witchcraft that function in
their father's house is now beginning to
attack her life she doesn't know why she
cannot keep a job because the mystery of
becoming one is not just one flesh they
are transactions that begin to take
place that this one can be maybe maybe
she just fell but she met a man that had
the spirit of immorality immorality from
the Marine Kingdom and she robs the
Spirit by the time she discovers she's
all over with everyone she's looking at
her life and she's saying but I think I
have good morals what is it that keeps
on making me mess up yet I know the
truth these interactions men go
collecting we are never told about this
we just think it was a good date we just
think something happened wrong no people
are
collecting that's why you look at a
person that is sexually active and
careless all over you never understand
their Dynamics one day she will wake up
as Kevin the next day she will wake up
as Eugene she doesn't even know herself
and I'm not just saying this to them
even them they begin to realize their
are tendencies that were not in
me and and you begin to see that the
enemy is very strategic in the end time
that is what he's releasing in a
generation because what happens if if
now she comes and gets married and in
her marriage she never dealt with some
of these things she has collected so
much this marriage might be shaken she
never burned the old bridges and now
anytime we are disagreeing she begins to
chat with
Eugene and maybe I discover the next
thing now this is a divorce and we are
separating by the time we separate there
is a child in between this child grows
knowing that children can grow without a
father and a mother we've already
doctrinated another
devorce by the time you are counting 20
25 years which is the age of a
generation you realize you have a
generation
that was not fathered it was not
mothered and it is a rebellious
generation they are growing by
themselves then you look at that Society
is a messed up Society but where did the
problem begin when sex lost its
place so we are fixing
generations and so now someone might ask
what does she need to
do to break and get free I bless the
Lord for one faith and I bless the Lord
for the santing blood of Jesus she wants
to get married she must come to an altar
and say Lord in the name of Jesus any
connection that I had with Kevin I
denounce it now anything I collected I
release whatever I collected from Eugene
I release it now I declare freedom I am
born again let the blood sanctify me and
wash me Kevin you are not in my life I
divorce you in the spirit Eugene you are
not in my life I divorce you in the
spirit and you make those
declarations and now by the time she
walks down the aisle there is no
legality in her life to oppose her
life is someone getting me people are
going live on internet celebrating body
counts what they don't know is beyond
how many did you sleep with is a
question how much did you collect and
that's why a person wants to settle in
marriage but they cannot settle because
they were creating a certain
dysfunctional order in the
spirit and that does not mean that the
two are safe the day they want to get
married is the same procedure they must
separate from all is someone getting me
we begin to collect things that were not
even in our
bloodline physical you can have your
seats the other
one there is something I call soul ties
that are initiated by spiritual
processes these are things that are
initiated by spiritual
processes I I didn't want to call them
spiritual Sal TI but they are Sal TI
initiated by spiritual
processes there are things that people
do unknowingly but they don't understand
they are exercising spiritual
keys there are things people do
unknowingly but they don't know the
exercising spiritual keys
have you ever realized when people walk
on the
altar when they exchange
vows we always declare them husband and
wives words they just poke and do you
know the vows that we tell men to
recite were creatively written by a man
in church they are not in the Bible
those vows they were creatively written
meaning that a vow is not just what you
make before an
altar there are people who are in
datings and relationships and they made
a vow and they said Over My Dead Body
I'll never date another woman and up to
now you are still looking for that girl
in other
girls what you don't know your own words
tied your
life a woman will look at a man and say
by the way the way I love you I rather
die rather than love another man those
are
vows those are spiritual Keys applied
and
knowingly you said I will never love
another man more than you now you are
married and the man you are married to
you don't love him more than the one you
used to date because that word still
stands as a legality in the spirit the
real of the spirit is very legalistic
Covenant and vows people agree and they
and they and they vow and they and they
say
things Valentine's just happened someone
is taken for a
date and that's why sometimes I'm
sensitive on
engagements if you know you're not
getting married in the next three or 6
months stop engaging that
girl because you're tying
her I remember I engaged my wife I think
it was we were going to her home on on
Saturday I engaged on Thursday I knew
now
n you two years
how and you know if you break up you
must
undo that I will marry you because if it
is not undone it will affect you it's a
reality in the spirit so a man goes down
on his knees tell him bro can you stand
up when is our marriage date is it
between 3 to 6 months okay go
down but a man is going down 5 years
later he's not talking no this is not a
political
[Music]
term someone must be
serious so please be sensitive the
things you say I'm talking about
exercising spiritual keys and
knowingly
unknowingly and these things affect
men just as I've said it takes two
people to stand on an altar and release
some words and they become realities in
their
lives the second one is what I call
blood
Covenant this used to be very common
when we're in primary school you go with
like a small meba and then you pierce
your hand and another one pierces his
hand and then you join your blood
and you say
forever you know love does not know age
the Bible says do not awaken love before
it's time meaning that a class six can
awaken
love I wish you could see some of us
class six we were
lovers we had nothing but we had
emotions and you have connected with
blood and I tell you blood
covenants are very
serious they are very
serious they are very serious some
people will oh this may sound and I'm
sorry for the language I don't know how
best I can put it some people will
intentionally sleep with a girl on her
menes because they understand the power
of blood Covenant
and they will casually tell you oh you
know when you sleep with a girl when
she's having a menes that girl will
never leave you there is a
revelation I even had another ultic man
saying that
even either by the blood of a virgin and
I don't know which day of our mes that
blood washes the star these
rituals somebody say blood Covenants
am I speaking to
anyone
[Music]
deliver is marriage is number one on
your prayer list go and divorce that
Covenant
the other one is spiritual
claims spiritual
claims people can claim you and most of
the times these spiritual claims are
done through witchcraft
[Music]
prayers someone has put you a photo in
their bathroom
or in their prayer closet every night
they are claiming you in the name of
Jesus you'll marry me I declare you'll
marry me any eye that tries to see you I
release blindness blindness
blindness before I got married a lady
went and bought a gown by
faith and she put it in her house and
she put my photo there
make a go no make a picture and you
begin to and you put there my husband my
wife you are a
[Music]
witch and every Sunday you see the
brother walking alone single or the
sister and you're saying thank you
angels of my destiny thank
you you're a witch
that's why you must you must denounce
any claim in the spirit there even
people were so careless they will even
meet you in church and tell you you know
the Lord told me you my
wife and then they will walk out with a
prayer angle the Lord I was in prayer
and the Lord just showed me and told me
you are my wife and then they will walk
out and they never show interest but
they have booked you in the spirit you
need to look for that brother and tell
him God is not afraid of me God stopped
sending angels in the Old Testament if
he spoke to you let him speak to me and
unbook
me yeah even ladies can come and tell
you that again before I married a lady
came and held my feet in a Prayer
Mountain she held my feet and cried and
said the Lord is saying the woman you're
are dating is not your
wife and I'm seeing a brown complexion
she's not your wife I looked at her then
I saw her posture in prayer I knew what
she was praying for so if she's not my
wife who's my wife why would God give
you gossips the Lord will have said this
is not your wife but this is your wife
and the way you have positioned yourself
in is in a man she said the Lord is
saying you need a pray a warrior a
prophetic wife I looked at her I said
those are your characteristics I know
you okay I didn't say it
loudly and guess what those things now
when you get married and you fight with
your wife they might show up as prophecy
and
say prophecy so I had to silence that
voice and say I know the voice of God
and I know marriage is the will of God
and I know this is the wife of my
destiny it is now too late for me to
walk
[Music]
out so beware of prophets
Pastor Ken is a victim here he
knows beware of
matchmakers there are people who know
who should marry who
matchmakers and sometimes the people we
thought were love birds they the ones
who break up those we thought they
didn't even know how to love each other
15 years later and you're like what they
did a simple wedding they didn't have
money this one was just walking to
church and this one now they've built
their driving beware of
matchmakers it's only even me even me
there are people I look and I say this
one has been
single but I can't even
suggest so that because I know it's only
God who knows their
Destiny for wife
potential but now you begin to say let
me just be a pastor in the name of Jesus
when you hear me sayos I'm saying Lord
open his eyes let him see the miracle is
next to
him
Hallelujah I have five minutes and then
I finish unfinished marriage processes
like
Rio unfinished marriage processes these
are things that create a certain claim
and a certain tie you began with someone
you went to the parents especially I
don't know about other cultures in the
kikuyu there's something called I don't
knowa and M
somethingand you know kand as in you go
and it's like a it's like what do I call
it's like an engagement service whereby
the the parents will call the girl and
and ask the girl are you telling us that
there will be no other man who will come
here to ask your hand in marriage and
the girl says yes and then they say now
are we permitted to eat these things and
they say yes and they eat you know that
statement has already closed the doors
in your father's house so people came
and did those things and they left and
then you disagreed and now you saying I
want to get married unless you undo that
thing it will speak in your
life and sometimes it's not even
necessary really returning what was
taken sometimes is you going back home
and telling your parents I know I told
you there is no other man who will ever
come that thing does not work now I want
to say again another man will come I
denounce
it and it happens both sides even men
can do it is that okay now I want to
finish with the last
one these are called demonic soul
ties demonic Sal ties are you learning
something yes are you learning something
tell your neighbor
neighbor mysteries in
a just tell that neighbor this this
season Pastor is a sage he's a man of
wisdom few scriptures and wisdom here
and there because I want to raise a very
balanced church I don't want people who
are speaking in tongues and they cannot
even settle a small conflict in the
house
yeah demonic Sal TI demonic Sal ties the
source of this demonic soul ties is when
a legal door is
opened is when a legal door is
opened and this one again it's quite
shameful and quite
debatable the same thing as
witchcraft when people that have grown
in witchcraft when you see them they
always know what witchcraft is some
people who have grown in
Nairobi they always think boss those
things don't exist now when we come to
this level where people get attacked
with what we call Incubus or succubus
Incubus is a male demon and sucubus is a
female
demon of course demons don't have gender
but they can take a familiar
shape now those of us and I'm saying us
that have been attacked by this spirit
we know it's a
reality but there are people who don't
even know that these things happened
some will call it oh you know it was wet
dreams yes how are you still W dreaming
at
35 if this was meant to be something
that happens in adolescence are you
trying to tell me you still an
adolescent and you see the enemy will
always want to put a blanket cover yes
so there's something called the incubus
that's the male it appears in a male
form and the succubus but these Spirits
are under a certain demon called
asmodus asmodus is the demon responsible
for
last and last is sexual legal appetite
that wants to be met in an ungodly way
that is last last is a sexual legal
appetite let me say this sexual desire
is legal
but how you meet it is what determines
the
illegality it is God who put those
Desires in your body and created
marriage as an Avenue where you ought to
now Express the desires and even the
Bible says that a woman will get a child
which is a very painful process but her
desire will still be for her
husband so there is a desire that God
put but is supposed to be channeled to a
man called your husband or your wife so
anytime we are meeting last in illegal
processes that is now where sin
enters but it's a legal appetite God
created it but at the end of the day
when it is met IL legally then at the
end of the day that is
SE and last is the source of all sexual
perversion last last is the source of
all sexual
perversion sometimes you see a man
married or a woman married and they
cheating in their marriage so the
question is it is not absence of sex
there must be a certain power
controlling that person and many people
think it's a moral issue but that issue
is sponsored by a certain power it is
called last and the core business of
these night demons or what we call
demonic solter The Core Business of this
attack is to baptize you with
lust they appear as a male they appear
as a female and sometimes they might
even want to initiate you with lasts
that are of other inclination that
you're a woman and you dreamt having sex
with another woman or you're a man you
dreamt having sex with another man
they're trying to plant ideas of
perversion this Spirit does not respect
single or married a man will fight with
his wife or a wife will fight with his
husband that night one of them will get
an attack you are just
sleeping you can't even talk to your
wife and then the demon will just come
and rest on one of you and you have very
strange dreams and your wife is there
because it has found a point of entry
and it is there to defile you when a
young man decides to walk in Purity the
day he makes the prayer and stays 4 days
walking in the pth the spirit manifests
because the spirit is trying to baptize
you with life last so that you can go
back to your
cycle a man that has been walking right
the spirit comes and defiles them and
begins to plant the essence of now them
being defiled because when we look at
spiritual real there are certain spirits
that defile a man there's a time I was
doing 21 days of prayer on the 20th day
that thing
appeared because sometimes in prayer you
pour yourself and you become empty
many Great Men of God they don't
backslide on Friday they backslide on
Monday or Sunday
evening why because after spiritual
outpouring you become empty and the
flesh becomes vulnerable and that's when
demons monitor people especially these
ones you see fire anointings
ministration because what that does it
draws everything in you if you don't
have a system of
refilling that means you have poured
over man if you don't have a system
where you feel my wife never understands
any time I finish preaching I always put
my earphones and I must hear what I
taught and she's like you're just from
preaching but I'm like if if I don't
refill I'll be
empty sometimes on Monday I have to
listen to a sermon because I must also
feel my
tank is someone getting me so this thing
this thing sometimes men go for prayer
7even days of fasting and they were just
praying in Tong 7 hours and what they
don't know as they were praying they
were just emptying themselves and at
night that thing shows up and you're
like I'm in prayer how come this thing
doesn't fear prayer no you are
vulnerable at that hour and it wants to
baptize you with the spirit of last some
environments are sensitive one day I
went to a hotel in meu as I slept I was
so tired fatigued coming from a
preaching session the spirit showed up
then I woke up the Lord told me pray for
this room this is this is a place where
many crazy things happened and that's
why sometimes you get to a room in a
lodging pray for it
Sanctified because you don't know what
activities happen there just say in the
name of Jesus as I sleep I sanctify this
bed I sanctify this place angels of my
destiny show up I will sleep because
that my covenantal right and sleep
Hallelujah so the core business is that
is there to baptize you with last this
thing will attack you in your
subconscious that's your sleep that
means it is a very high level
battle because if I'm in my
Consciousness I can say no if I'm in
subconscious it means anything can
happen because that's my very vulnerable
moment so this does not mean that when
you get an attack of this Spirit it
doesn't mean you're not prayerful it
doesn't mean there's something wrong you
have done sometimes it's nothing wrong
it's just an attack to defile you and to
release the spirit of lust lust will
never lead you to your
wife lust will begin to open doors of
expression some of these Spirits are
very common in Marine areas where sex is
very dominant but there are 13 major
doors that are open that kind of manage
and help these spirits to have legality
there are 13 I'm going to mention them
quickly number one is pornography these
13 dolls are very key number one is the
do of pornography last Thursday I did a
sermon on pornography please if you get
time go and watch it I did a sermon on
pornography on Thursday in the Gathering
of Champions number one is pornography
number two is
masturbation number two is
masturbation masturbation this is
becoming a very common practice among
many people masturbation will never it
doesn't have physical
consequences it is a very private
shameful scene and we are seeing people
trying to normalize it in our
day masturbation it opens a door for
this attack legally it will come without
question number three is rape or
molestation many people that have gone
through sexual abuse doors are open for
many things and even some of the doors
open sometimes is always
perversion you sit down and begin to see
people that have certain
inclination maybe they behaving like
lesbians they're behaving in a certain
Gaye way sometimes some of them and not
all of them sometimes some of them
possibly they underwent some sexual
abuse and AD Dove manipulation and
control was opened rape and
molestation and this happens when people
are very young number four we have
verbal or physical abuse veral or
physical abuse this one happens a lot in
marriages and
relationships verble or physical abuse
someone can tell you a word and you just
wish they slapped
you some words are more painful than
even physical
pain verbal or physical abuse and that's
why anytime as a couple you're having a
conversation please be very sensitive of
what you're saying to the other person
words can never be returned
no matter how much sorry you say they
can never be returned there are people
who it is like they intentionally speak
to
heart and this one opens the door
sometimes a man is silent because he's
hurting or a woman is silent because the
kind of words you're throwing to them
they just decide to keep quiet for peace
sake you could be opening a door in a
person's life number five unforgiveness
and bitterness
this is not just a door for these
spirits but this is a door for many
demonic attacks and forgiveness and
bitterness unforgiveness and bitterness
the devil loves bitter
people the devil loves people that are
unforgiving I've I've I've attended
churches and you find there's a meeting
I attended and I'm sorry to say I'm
saying this with a lot of love and I
discovered that meeting was full of
women and then I interrogated father I
discovered much majority of those women
were
hurting and then I looked at the man on
the pulpit and the kind of prayers that
were being made I said I don't know why
but I I feel there's a
problem it had everything to do with
cursing killing my enemies Must Die
whoever whoever Rises against me I
scatter you know there are prayers that
are
bitter and and when and inside some
meetings when you get and say it doesn't
matter what the enemies are going
through you see people standing
you're like forgive and release it can't
be perpetually you have
enemies some people you forgive them
they are your enemies but you left them
one man said when you go when there is a
boxing match and you fail to show up in
the ring there is no
match if your opponent is waiting in the
ring and you fail to show up there's no
war forgive to kill the
war and bitterness and and they said
bitterness is the source of many
diseases even
today because that emotional imbalance
messes chemical balances in your
body
ulcers things are coming up number six
is
pain people that have gone through
pain number
seven fasting and spiritual
warfare and I've mentioned about prayer
sometimes most of our prayers we go and
empty
ourselves number eight
fornication and
adultery number eight fornication and
adultery number nine number eight
fornication and adultery number nine
Canal canity you are perpetually In the
Flesh you don't pray you don't read the
word the things you're watching the
things you're listening to Canal
number
10 fear and
doubt this one kills your Spiritual
Authority fear and doubt fear and doubt
number 11
witchcraft
witchcraft number 12 emotional
wounds they become a gate there's a lady
and these are true story
because she was dating one of my
pastors and every relationship when she
approach
marriage this spirit will show up
intensively and she will get discourage
and cancel the
thing so my pastor is sitting with her
and the lady says I'm
suicid I don't know why I don't feel
like living and then you're looking at
life and you're saying is this a w I
want to live with the way I'm visioning
life and later we discovered she grew
and her parents were
pastors she grew in a
home where the father was very abusive
to the mother and her and in her young
age every night she will dream her
playing with a young boy as she grew the
boy grew
as she reached a certain age the boy had
sex with her and that never stopped no
it became like every night she'll have a
dream having sex and any time she fought
it now became violent it became like now
this thing is now ripping her it reached
a place she began to see babies coming
at night to
Circle anytime she wants to get married
that thing will show up and this time
she got into prayer and
the the demon manifested and said you
are
mine it took prayers of a few generals
to break that
thing so what was the entry emotional
wounds the the and and some people of
that nature their
Destinies are in
marriage because in the doors of Destiny
some people blessings are in
marriage and number number 13 another
door that is opened is when now you have
when you have soul ties with a bound
person you have a soul tie with a person
that is perpetually visited by these
Spirits it opens a
door I met a certain lady who were
praying for her and the only thing the
man needed to do was to sleep with her
and the man was coming from a marine
Kingdom and what the man had purpose to
do was sleep with her and initiate her
and steal her
Destiny so the lady was not advancing
and no one was marrying her at 40 no one
is marrying her she really wants to
settle but someone just needed to use
the Gate of sex for there to be a
transfer of a marine power and every
time she wanted to walk out these things
will appear it's always a shameful thing
because many people always think it's my
mistake when a door let me just look at
a door like like a door of emotional
wounds or a door of verbal and physical
abuse these are doors that have nothing
to do with you you're just expressing
yourself and someone releases words and
a spirit finds an opportunity for
attack but let me tell you any time
there is an attack of this Spirit
anytime the core reason of that attack
is to release the spirit of last is
someone getting me is the spirit of lust
and that sometimes can also come is a
demonic
comfort you break up with someone
they've wounded you and then the spirit
begins to visit you and it looks like
it's a demonic Comfort you've argued
with your wife or your husband and the
thing visits you and it looks like a
demonic comfort so what do a person does
when a person wakes up in the morning
just look at yourself and say in the
name of Jesus last cannot live in
me you Incubus and sucubus and your
family you will not baptize me with last
these are called prayers of
denunciation they are prayers of
announcing but there are things with
denounce is someone getting me
denouncing means an attack has been
launched to program you in a certain
order but you are refusing it and you
are saying it cannot happen in my
life that that's the and you make that
Prayer by faith you may not feel
anything but you make that Prayer by
faith but before before we end this
service we are going to close every
door
Hallelujah your sleep will be the
covenantal sleep of God you will see
Angels ascending and
descending as I Was preparing yesterday
night the Lord just gave me these nine
points and I want to mention them
because I believe is someone's prayer
today they may not be very much related
but I as as I was going to sleep the
Lord just told me go back and he gave me
nine points and these are points why
some people face prolonged
singlehood why some people face
prolonged singlehood allow me to mention
them then we going to pray today I'll
call an aacle because I need to pray for
men that need to break this language of
prolonged singlehood number
one number one there are people that
have been on a prolonged singlehood
number one because of wrong spiritual
identity wrong spiritual Identity or
what I call the wrong branding in the
spirit people meet you and they tell
you marriage then you ask
yourself is there anage that we look and
say maringo it means there is an
identity that blocks access and that
identity and branding must be dealt with
and if you're here in this service and
this has been your issue I declare by
this Revelation may the Lord restore
your identity may the Lord restore the
real you where there is a distortion of
who you are don't just take the
statements of men casually that is what
they are seeing but what you know who
you are is not what they are
saying I dealt with this thing I will
meet with people and the first thing
they will say
and it used to hurt me I want to get
serious in a relationship and a girl
will laugh and say
ah and you're serious I discovered you
can carry a wrong
branding number two is generational
patterns where people do not
marry some of you you must wrestle this
thing and tell the Lord now that I'm in
Christ this thing is going to be broken
by me it is not going to bring me down
number three there's something we call
traditional
claims traditional claims so there's
generational patterns traditional claims
Chris you'll agree with me among the
cber communities there is always a girl
that is supposed to stay with the
father that girls are born and then you
hear this one is the one who will stay
with the father at home and when that
girl tries to go out is it looks like
there is a claim you need to stay with
the father even among the
kikus you need to understand that is a
claim in the spirit you need to
disconnect from that father
claim number
four these are things that makes people
stay long and healed wounds from past
relationships and what do these wounds
provoke and healed wounds from past
relationships if you find a man man that
is 30 years and above and still single
please ask him what
happened that man could be looking for
his ex in the next girl or that woman
there are people who search for people
in other
people and healed wounds this one
happened to a person I know very
closely this person really loved the
girl it was his first love and the girl
broke his heart as early as those days
of compass the girl broke his heart up
to now the man is still struggling
around 42 years he has not married and
any time he picks that the name of that
girl must come up so in his mind every
girl that comes he must we with the
first girl there are people who have not
moved on because they are looking for
the girl or the man and listen the
person you will get is not that girl or
that man is an individual so there must
be
healing careless confessions and I
mentioned the this I'll never get
married careless
confessions witchcraft number six this
very serious Destinies are tied and
sometimes there are people who are
attacked not because they're the ones in
the wrong because they know they're
trying to frustrate the joy of your
mother so someone is fighting Your
Mother by tying your
destiny or sometimes you get married and
you can't get a child because someone is
trying to fight the joy of your
parents and that's why you need to arise
as a personal
intercessor number seven is Attack on
Destiny attack on Destiny marriage is a
door of Destiny and some people
blessings are in marriage so the enemy
has camped on that door and is's saying
no you can't enter Because the day you
get married things open
up I am a victim of
marriage I did High School missions for
more than 10
years when this woman came my
wife things shifted 2017 21st October we
got married 2018 we open the church and
you study my life from 2018 it is on an
upward level there's a place I had
stagnated some of you the problem is not
a eration is that this door is where the
blessings
lie she didn't come with money she
didn't come with anything she just came
with the grace to complete a certain
phase of my life so that things can move
forward and that's why you must cry for
this door if you know this is the door
some people have delayed because of
studies and
career you are now on your fourth degree
the day you lift up your head you're 45
and
career one of my friends told me
every success comes with a
prize sometimes you study the men at the
top but the prize is their family you
study a corporate woman at the top but
the price is her
marriage I sat down with my friend and
and he told me he's called like me he
told me I respect my
wife just having a man conversation he
told me never silence the voice of your
wife in
marriage give her audience because they
speak wisdoms sometimes in Simplicity
and he told me you know my wife decided
to forsake her career for 5 years so
that she can raise our children and he
told me boss I'm a senior man manager I
also want to brag and say my wife is a
director in a certain place not a
housewife but she sacrificed her career
so that she can raise the children now
the children are past 5 years old she's
gone back to her
career and he told me that thing touched
my heart because very few people will
give that sacrifice and he said it was
an honor for me as a man and as a father
so we need to balance and ask am I
gaining something
by losing something I cannot
gain sometimes you lose something you'll
never gain trying to pursue something
you're going to gain remember losing a
family sometimes or marriage sometimes
gaining it might be
impossible but you can always get
another
job I've seen people who've traveled out
of the
country I remember a friend of mine is a
DJ he was going to study in South Africa
he took the whole of his family and said
take Daddy to
school he told me it looks foolish but
he said I could not repay back those 5
years it's sometimes at the top when you
realize the decision I made was not the
right one am I speaking to anyone
yes years
bro there's a Time men made a joke and
they told one of a pastor I know next
time you go to America for two months
we'll bring your wife you can't
disappear for that
long number
nine there are people who have stayed in
prolonged singlehood because of wrong
models of
marriage the people that modeled
marriage modeled the wrong thing I have
spent your time but I believe this was
Noble let me receive the worshippers I
just want to make one prayer have you
learned something have you learned
something I I want to make a
prayer and number
one and this nobody should be ashamed of
this I want to pray for number one
people that are saying
[Music]
pastor this nature of my
singlehood carries a spiritual
element I can see and I sense there is a
prolonged there is a delay that doesn't
make sense and number two if you are
there and you sense
pastor this matter of night
demons is a matter I need to address
don't be ashamed even as all of us stand
on our feet
I'll just encourage those people to come
at the front because I want to pray for
you I just want to pray for you this is
a matter of Destiny and I've put it very
clearly these attacks don't come
sometimes because you did anything wrong
but there is a level of that attack that
must be broken there is a level that it
must be
broken there are Thrones
[Music]
just come to the altar don't be afraid I
know I'm pastoring a young Church These
are some of the things that men are
dealing with and struggling with but I
thank the Lord there is an anointing and
the Lord cannot just send me to come and
speak a message without a cause as we
are singing this song they are Thrones
they are kingdoms but only
yesu there are kingom and please don't
be afraid don't be afraid
mountains and there are Thrones there is
an open Heaven only a sure we came for
deliverance
forever for those who are with the
cameras I encourage all the cameras to
face
me all the cameras to face me anytime we
are doing an ALT call we are not here to
try and put anybody face on the camera
an Alaco is a private matter it's a man
coming to seek the help of Zion so just
lift up your hands begin to pray I will
join you in prayer even as we release
this song those that are standing there
please let's agree with them in prayer
there must be Deliverance there must be
doors that are going to be closed in
your life there must be Cycles there
must be something that the enemy is
trying to fight in your life and that's
why at this hour by I took time to lay
that foundation so that you may
understand this is not just another
dream this is not just another encounter
there must be deposit there are things
that are trying to be intercepted we
refuse to be ignorant we know the
realities of Zion we know the
possibilities of Heaven these are
attacks is not an indwelling it's an
attack perpetually showing up in my
dreams perpetually manifesting right now
in the name of Jesus I begin to close
any door that will open upon your life
let the Holy Ghost let the power of the
Holy Ghost begin to deliver men let that
power deliver for you it is a marine
Dimension it is a marine Kingdom be
delivered be delivered be delivered let
the yolks of Darkness let them be broken
over your life let the yolks of the
devil let them be broken over your life
every demonic Sal we break it right now
every Eugene are you you to walk around
and begin to lay your hands on these
people get me the anointing oil the
Bible says the anointing breaks the Yoke
we are going to anoint you and that yoke
is going to be broken that yoke is going
to be broken When I Was preparing for
this service I had the word deliverance
and I had the word freedom and this is
the day of your freedom let the captives
be set free some of you you are innocent
some of you it's because of you you are
just caught up in a crossfire rapali as
a fire somebody has been using
witchcraft to manipulate your destiny
somebody has been using an altar to make
sure that there is no advancement over
your life today in the name of Jesus
there must be a turn around there must
be a turn around your destiny must be
released your destiny must be released
the doors that were open they must be
closed they must be closed the fire of
God is here people are already receiving
their Deliverance that's it my sister
let that thing leave you let it leave
you let it leave you I command it to
leave you wherever it came from live
that life live that Destiny wherever you
came from live that life the spirit of
lust will not dominate over your life
some of these demons have been trying to
recruit you into lesbianism into gism
there have been perversive dreams we
close that channel in the reals of the
spirit some appear as relaties trying to
initiate you into the real of I take
authority
now we cancel every perversive Spirit we
command you to live we command you to
live we command you to live we command
you to live every blood Covenant we
cancel it now
who is
kingom if you there begin to lift up
pray begin to lift up pray let us agree
let us agree
to his
kingom to his
kingom
listen I declare this oil will land of
you like purifying fire the Bible says
the anointing breaks the York I declare
by this oil this is an instruction we
know the oil is a symbol of the Holy
Ghost our faith is not in the oil but I
hear the Holy Ghost tell me anoint them
now because they are going to rise under
the freshness of that anointing I
declare as the oil lands on you whatever
troubled you is coming to an end
whatever that has affected you is coming
to an end in the mighty name of Jesus in
the mighty name of Jesus even for them
that are online I release the same
anointing let the oil of the spirit
locate you wherever you are let the oil
of the spirit locate you wherever you
are we break emotional ties we break
physical ties we break ties that were
initiated by spiritual rituals we break
demonic ties whatever that has tied your
destiny there are people that are not
advancing because of broken relationship
it's time for you to begin to advance
every broken Spirit every broken wound
let it be healed right now let it be
healed right
now be on
theer the fire the fire the fire of God
is coming upon you the fire of God is
coming upon you receive that anointing
sh lay hands on them anoint them anoint
them anoint them freedom is coming
freedom is coming freedom is coming
freedom is coming freedom is coming the
spirit of Liberty the spirit of Liberty
who is
King to is King
to his
King to his
kingom to his
kingom to his keep oh
yes
let the Y be broken let the let be free
let them be set free Deliverance is
coming healing is coming we open the
doors of marriage we open the doors of
marriage we open the doors of marriage
a generation must be delivered a
generation must be delivered a
generation must be delivered
I see the chains of Witchcraft releasing
some Destiny anyone pound by the chains
of Witchcraft I losen you
now any altar that speaks in your
father's house that hinders men from
advancing I declare the anointing to
rise above it is upon your life you are
a car of God you are a car of God you
are a car of God let this thing let this
matter be
settled I command witchcraft live that
life live that life live that life live
that life live it now in Jesus
name oh thank
you if you're here and nobody has
anointed you lift up your
hand that you have not been
anointed oh my God I need more
workers I need more
workers listen please hold her hold
on if nothing happens take her to the to
the vest take her to the vest
[Music]
Tre can it's
okay I'm looking for mature men in the
spirit that can carry these assignment
mom Esther
come I want you to lay hands on these
people I sense an
anointing thank you Holy Ghost
thank you Holy
[Music]
Ghost thank you Holy
Spirit there is there is Deliverance
I kept on hearing the Lord telling me
he's he's delivering men from
witchcraft some of you whatever you are
dealing with is not just ordinary power
is the power of
Witchcraft and now in the name of Jesus
the name that is above every name anyone
Bound by witchcraft any Destiny tied to
an altar I take authority in the name
name of Jesus be loosen now let your
life be released let your destiny be
released I Lift Your Name from that
altar I Lift Your Name from that altar
be set
free
[Music]
sh thank you Holy Ghost if you've not
been anointed lift up your hand I think
I need to join this team Please Release
a worship
[Music]
consuming
fire sweet
perfume his
aome
presence FS this
place for this is
Holy Ground
so and
bow
down
consuming
fire sweet
perfum his
awesome
presence feel
his this is Holy Ground this is Holy
Ground this is Holy Ground
consuming
fire his
awesome
awesome oh this is all ground this is
all ground this
is you are consuming fire
cons
aome
aome this
place this place this is Holy this
is this
is you are consuming
fire
you're feel this BL feel this BL oh this
is ho
ground Holy Ground Holy
Ground you are consum
fireus
aesome awesome
Jesus
Jesus for this is only
ground this is only ground this is all
ground
so so
God we are standing on the Holy Ground
oh God
God for this is the
holy
the so
and through
me thank you Holy
Ghost
for ho
them that are kneeling stand stand on
your
feet father we give you
glory the power to heal the power to
deliver is in you there is no man that
can take any
credit I announce a new dawn over your
life and I declare from this hour those
visitations are
illegal and them that that have been
dealing with
prolonged prolonged
singlehood because of certain spiritual
factors I announce right now let the
doors of marriage open up for you this
is a gate of Destiny and anyone that is
not ordained for your life I declare
they will not locate you may them that
were ordained from the foundations of
the Earth let them locate you from this
hour in the mighty name name of Jesus I
declare the sound of the bridegroom and
the sound of the groom and the sound of
weddings will begin to be heard again in
your homes and in your communities and
marriages will begin to work in the
mighty name of Jesus I pray for every
marriage in this house I cancel the
spirit of divorce I declare the wisdom
of sustenance and I declare the
abilities to build in the ways of the
Lord father we give you glory
the only prayer I want to make maybe if
you're there and you are not born again
just lift up your hand and I'm going to
pray with you in this atmosphere if
you're there and you're not born again
just lift up your hand thank you is
there anyone else you are not born again
you are not born again just stay here
let me make this prayer then I'm going
to release you thank you thank you
wherever you are just I see another hand
over there thank you I see I see I see
two hands thank you my God let me tell
you something
church sometimes these 10 minutes could
be be sting a destiny that has suffered
for 30 years so let us I'm I'm happy
that you you guys have the respect I
know we have past our time but you never
know the operation taking
place that's why such Ms for me you
suspend the watch a little bit because
this could be a moment of the woman
flowing with the issue of blood that for
12 years this is what she was waiting
for Hallelujah and I believe that
something is happening in this house
praise the Lord praise the Lord oh thank
you I see oh thank you we have three
ladies who are here is there anyone else
coming to receive Jesus thank you
there's another hand over there please
ashers just help them to come to the
front let's celebrate them even as they
are coming it all begins at
Salvation it all begins at
Salvation thank you thank you thank you
oh my God there is harvest in the house
I told the Lord if this be the year of
harvest I want to see the first harvest
which is salvation thank you my sister
today is a new day for you them that
have lifted up their hands and them that
have have found their way to the front
thank you I want you to I want you to
repeat this prayer after me say Lord
Jesus today willingly I come to you
knowing that I'm a sinner in need of a
savior and today by faith I receive
receive a etal life today I confess with
my mouth because I have believed in my
heart that Jesus you are Lord over my
life thank you for saving me father I
thank you for everyone that has made
that prayer it is only you who can save
sustain and keep and declare the grace
to stand and withstand I declare that
you'll fill them with your Holy Spirit
fill them with the hunger to Know You by
reading the word and even feel them
release men to walk with them in
discipleship thank you for this Harvest
and even for the many oh God that will
listen to this message and give their
lives to you father we honor you and we
glorify you in Jesus name we have
prayed hallelujah hallelujah hallelujah
them that have gotten born again I'll
encourage you just walk outside there
there will be someone to receive you and
that someone will also help you we'll
get your number and someone will reach
out to you so that they can we can begin
to disciple you even as we had a day
like
this let's celebrate them once again
Church please turn to your neighbor tell
your neighbor neighbor thank you for
your
maturity that even though time has gone
you have still stayed in this
atmosphere and now I declare any other
need in this house
things that people were believing God
for healings
doors
supplies anything that you came as a
need may my God who supplies all things
may he supply all your needs according
to his riches in glory I declare under
this environment whatever that you have
been believing God for may you receive
it now in the mighty name of Jesus those
doors those healings those Miracles
those breakthroughs Whatever It Is With
God all things are possible amen and
amen hallelujah you guys can go and take
your seat and victory is your portion
what has happen today it is
permanent
[Applause]
hallelujah hallelujah